Guide to the Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, Photographs of Events, Activities, and Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, photographs of events, activities, and individuals
1870-1934
RU 766
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4
(4 boxes)
The materials consist of photographs documenting faculty, students, alumni, and activities of the Yale Sheffield Scientific School.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 31-H (YRG 31-H), Audio-visual materials and memorabilia documenting the Sheffield Scientific School.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs documenting faculty, students, alumni, and activities of the Yale Sheffield Scientific School.
Photographs; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Sheffield Scientific School
- Photographs, Series I
  - Photographs of students, clubs, and activities (Box 1)
  - Class records: Student Councils (oversize), 1911-1928 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
- Photographs of individuals in the civil and sanitary engineering programs at Yale, 1879-1933; Accession 19ND-A-444
  - Group photographs
    - circa 1879-1883 (Box 1)
    - 1890-1899 (Box 1)
    - 1900-1931 (Box 1)
  - Group photographs (Oversize)
    - 1883-1907 (Box 2)
    - 1905-1911 (Box 2)
    - 1900-1911 (Box 2)
    - 1910-1931 (Box 2)